{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Hey!",
      "answer": "Hello!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hi!",
      "answer": "Hello!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Let me know your questions and I'll be happy to answer",
      "answer": "Could you tell me about the company culture, how has your time been there and is it a good workplace for young individuals to grow?"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are your questions",
      "answer": "Would you say that the impact is visible in a big company such as yours?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you have any questions",
      "answer": "Would you say that the impact is visible in a big company such as yours?"
    },
    {
      "question": "please let me know your questions",
      "answer": "Would you say that the impact is visible in a big company such as yours?"
    },
    {
      "question": "what questions do you have",
      "answer": "Would you say that the impact is visible in a big company such as yours?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please send me your resume",
      "answer": "I'll send you my Resume ASAP"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can refer you",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "apply with this link for my referral",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "I can provide you a referral",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "I can provide you a referral if you send me your resume and req ID",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you please send me the job link which you want referral for, your first name, last name and email id, so that I can refer you",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "Ping me on the weekends",
      "answer": "Sure! We can schedule a call at your convenience"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sorry my team has no matched opening right now",
      "answer": "I understand! Thank you for your response! I'll be on the lookout for future opportunities"
    },
    {
      "question": "All the best in your search",
      "answer": "Thank you!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hi, no openings on my team",
      "answer": "I understand! Thank you for your response! I'll be on the lookout for future opportunities"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good luck with your search!",
      "answer": "Thank you!"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can refer you to a role if you have a req in mind",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "Let\u2019s connect next week",
      "answer": "Sure! We can schedule a call at your convenience"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please visit careers page",
      "answer": "I will. Thanks for the tip!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please reach out to the recruiter.",
      "answer": "I will. Thanks for the tip!"
    },
    {
      "question": "please let me know any questions you have about the job search process",
      "answer": "Could you tell me about the company culture, how has your time been there and is it a good workplace for young individuals to grow?"
    },
    {
      "question": "Send me the positions you are interested in along with your resume. I can refer",
      "answer": "I'll send you my Resume ASAP"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you share the resume and link to",
      "answer": "I'll send you my Resume ASAP"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you need referral, I am happy to do it.",
      "answer": "Thank you so much for the offer. I'll look for relevant opportunities and get back to you."
    },
    {
      "question": "How are you doing?",
      "answer": "I'm doing well thanks for asking!"
    }
  ]
}